greatdealcompare.com 2018-05-08

# Great Deal Compare

**Last updated: June 2016**  
Great Deal Compare cares about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. We respect the privacy of our users and are committed to protect the personal information that you share with us in connection with the use of Great Deal Compare. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe our practices regarding the information we collect from you when you use Great Deal Compare, the manners in which we may use such information, and the options and rights available to you. This privacy policy applies to both our downloadable browser add-on application or our website at the address http://www.discountmag.net (collectively and separately known as “Great Deal Compare”), brought to you (the “User”, “you”) by AdOptim. (“we”, “us”, or the “Company”).  
BY ACCESSING OR USING GREAT DEAL COMPARE YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, PLEASE DO NOT INSTALL, ACCESS, OR USE GREAT DEAL COMPARE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER, AND PROMPTLY ERASE AND REMOVE GREAT DEAL COMPARE AND ANY PART THEREOF FROM YOUR SYSTEMS.  
USER CONSENT  
You are not obligated by law to provide us with any information. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you are providing us with information at your own free will, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and that we may retain such information in accordance with this Policy and any applicable laws and regulations.

 **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We collect Non-personal and Personal Information in order to provide and operate Great Deal Compare and to make Great Deal Compare and related services customized as possible to your interests and preferences. We also use the information for statistical and analytics, research and technical support; this enable us to further develop, customize and improve Great Deal Compare based on Users’ common preferences and uses and to enable us to provide our Users with a better user experience, with more relevant products, offers and deals and other marketing materials. We make sure you get the best price every time! The following are the types of data and information from our Users:  
a. Non-personally identifiable information pertaining to a User, which may be made available or gathered via the User’s use of Great Deal Compare (“Non-personal Information”). We are not aware of the identity of the User from which the Non-personal Information was collected. Non-personal Information which is being collected consists of technical information and aggregated usage information, and may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on Great Deal Compare, type of operation system, User’s ‘click-stream’ on Great Deal Compare’s offers and any e-commerce websites operated by third parties (including Third Party Services, as such term is defined in the Terms), including search queries and related searches on search engines you make, browser type and version, language and keyboard language.  
b. The second type of information is personally identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, or may be of private or sensitive nature (“Personal Information”).Personal Information which is may be gathered consists of the following: The User’s IP address or other persistent user identifier, which is allocated to your device by your Internet service provider and used mainly for enhancing the User’s experience and for geolocation personalization, as further detailed below; Any Personal Information provided voluntarily by the User via Great Deal Compare, such as the User’s e-mail address in order to be contacted or any Users interaction with us through Great Deal Compare, as may be updated from time to time by us. We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your consent, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the Privacy Policy. Please note that even if you will voluntarily submit your personal information to us, we do not merge such information with pseudonymous information we may have collected about you, and we do not supplement such information with other sources.

**WAYS WE COLLECT INFORMATION**  
We use certain technologies and methods to collect information: a. Cookies; a cookie is A ‘cookie’ is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to recognize you as a User and so we will be able to provide you with customized Offers. You will need to have cookies enabled in order to use and enjoy our services. We use cookies to collect and correlate certain information about you as detailed in section 10 herein.  
b. Keys and values in the Windows Registry; which include data about your operating system and relevant processes;  
c. Installer Reports; when you install Great Deal Compare, the installer generates reports with information about the installation of Great Deal Compare on your computer;  
d. Information which you provide us voluntarily; For example, we collect Personal Information which you voluntarily provide when you contact us directly by email for instance.  
We store the Personal Information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below.  
We value your privacy and control over your personal information, and therefore you may notify us that you wish to either review your Personal Information or delete it. You can notify us by sending an email to: [EMAIL] and we will make reasonable efforts to delete any such Personal Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws. Note that unless you instruct us otherwise we may retain your Personal Information for a period of 12 months or a longer period as reasonably and legally required.  
If you are a resident of California, United States, or of the European Union, you have the right to send us written request and ask a list of Personal Information categories that we may disclosed to third parties or to which we may give access to third parties, and the details of such third parties. To exercise such right you may contact us at: Support@discountmag.net

 **Links to Third Party Websites**  
Great Deal Compare is a directory of offers at third party sites. You will be transferred to online merchants or other third party sites through links on Great Deal Compare. Great Deal Compare is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and our Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by those sites. Before using third party sites, you should read and understand those sites’ privacy policies to ensure you agree to their terms.  
At all times you can choose not to allow us or any third party to collect data about you, or ask to view or edit Personal Information that is stored about you. You may also choose not to accept cookies, including cookies associated with our services or third party services. However, you should take into account that many of the services or portion of them may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.  
Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law We may disclose information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or if we consider it necessary to maintain service and improve our products and services. 

**Minors**  
To install and use Great Deal Compare you must be over the age of thirteen (13). The Company does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of thirteen (13) are not using Great Deal Compare.

**Security**  
We take a great care in implementing and maintaining the security of Great Deal Compare and your Personal Information. The Personal Information is hosted on our server which provides advanced security features. The Company employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its Users’ Personal Information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access. If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with our Policy, please contact us directly at contact@greatdealcompare.com and our privacy officer shall investigate promptly.  
Third party software/service  
While using Great Deal Compare we may be using third party software or service, in order to collect and process the information detailed herein. Such software includes without limitation, Google Analytics, which privacy policy is available at http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.

 **Cookies**  
When you access or use Great Deal Compare we use industry-wide technologies such as “cookies” (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer (“Local Storage”) and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your service experience much more convenient and effortless. The cookies used by Great Deal Compare are created per session you launch when the application starts for the first time, and may persist until the application is removed from your computer. We do not include any information about you other than your session and anonymous globally unique identifier key, the date and time at which you have started using the application, information about how you have downloaded Great Deal Compare to your computer and information necessary to serve you different content, such as when performing user-interface so-called “A/B tests”. These cookies can be removed by using your browser’s cookie/Local Storage cleaning facilities. It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage altogether. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited.  
The list below provides additional information regarding the types of cookies we use and their purpose:  
Functionality Cookies: used to identify you as an user and you preferences to provide you with customized offers and deals; we also use such cookies to label you as an opted-out user in case you will choose to opt out of our services;  
Analytics Cookies: used to collect information about how users use Great Deal Compare. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve Great Deal Compare. Such information is collected in an aggregated form, including the number of Users of Great Deal Compare, where Users have access to Great Deal Compare from and the webpages they visited.

 **Information warranty disclaimer**  
Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we are not responsible for the accuracy, correctness and security of any of the information we gather, store and disclose to you or to anyone else. 

**Changes to the privacy policy**  
The Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and at its sole discretion, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this Privacy Policy on our homepage and we will notify you via Great Deal Compare regarding such changes. such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on any of the above mentioned methods. otherwise, all other changes to this privacy policy are effective as of the stated “last updated” date and your continued use of Great Deal Compare after the last revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.
